What's new? 	lela xbmc skin 


r115	adjustment: DialogKaiToast.xml, new backgrounds and label style (visible when you put a USB Stik to the Port큦). Finished 	Today (7 minutes ago)	alwinker...@gmx.de
r114	changed: changed: strings.xml큦 german, language and Label codes "Datenbank Mode" to "Datenbank" and from the Library back, to "Datenbank". adjustment: DialogKaiToast.xml, new backgrounds and label style (visible when you put a USB Stik to the Port큦). 	Today (40 minutes ago)	alwinker...@gmx.de
r113	changed: bigxmas.png	Dec 05 (42 hours ago)	alwinker...@gmx.de
r112	add: bic xmas picture to all screens	Dec 05 (2 days ago)	alwinker...@gmx.de
r111	adding: default button noFocus at Home Top Buttons	Dec 05 (2 days ago)	alwinker...@gmx.de
r110	adding: Reset SkinSettings Option	Dec 05 (2 days ago)	alwinker...@gmx.de
r109	adding: xmas Style in the skin-settings for(enable/disable) and at home its visible	Dec 04 (2 days ago)	alwinker...@gmx.de
r108	adding: BIG Button images (home-submenu) many images	Dec 04 (3 days ago)	alwinker...@gmx.de
r107	changed: name of the theme, lela -> default.xpr	Dec 03 (4 days ago)	alwinker...@gmx.de
r106	adding: BIG Button images (home-submenu) Kids, Last.fm, wua.la	Dec 03 (4 days ago)	alwinker...@gmx.de
r105	adjustment: Visible BIG Button images (homemenu) if activate in the Skin Settings, now visible only if the specific button has Focus. Currently only 2 Button images aviable (lelaloader update Button and xbmc exit button).	Dec 03 (4 days ago)	alwinker...@gmx.de
r104	changed: Progressbar Style in the Visualization, adding: a option to Visible the procent labels at this progressbar (SkinSettings) 	Dec 02 (4 days ago)	alwinker...@gmx.de
r103	adjustment: FontSize and positions at the SettingsCategory.xml (menu)
r102	update: first skin theme, name: lela.xpr update: "on working folder" -> new icons	Today (6 minutes ago)	alwinker...@gmx.de
r101	changed: many translations from English to German language. add: first skin theme, name: lela.xpr add: on working folder	Today (2 hours ago)	alwinker...@gmx.de
r100	add: date and revisions label for the beta phase of the skin in the home menu	Nov 29 (2 days ago)	alwinker...@gmx.de
r99		changed: many translations from English to German language.	Nov 29 (2 days ago)	alwinker...@gmx.de
r98		adjustment: FontSize and positions at the musicOSDVisSettings	Nov 18, 2008	alwinker...@gmx.de
r97		adjustment: FontSize and positions at the Video OSD Settings	Nov 17, 2008	alwinker...@gmx.de
r96		changed: strings.xml큦 german,english language and Label codes "Datenbank Modus" in "Datenbank" and from the Library back to "Datei Modus".	Nov 08, 2008	alwinker...@gmx.de
r95		change: position of the Volume status, remove the memory status.	Nov 06, 2008	alwinker...@gmx.de
r94		edit: Credits text new: slider_nibFO.png and media/button-cd-focus.png	Nov 03, 2008	alwinker...@gmx.de
r93		adjustment: FontSize and positions at the single Category selected backgrounds menu. (Home,Movies,Picture,Music etc....) custom3.xml changed: Font Album-Label @ musicVisualisation.	Nov 02, 2008	alwinker...@gmx.de
r92		update changlog.xml
r91		adjustment: FontSize and positions at the PluginSetup/SettingsMenu.	Today (2 minutes ago)	alwinker...@gmx.de
r90		adjustment: FontSize and positions at the default Settings Menu.	Yesterday (17 hours ago)	alwinker...@gmx.de
r89		adjustment: background size in this Dialog Windows add: TOP 100 in the Music SubMenu @ Home	Oct 29 (2 days ago)	alwinker...@gmx.de
r88		add: SkinSettingsMenu a new option with shortcuts. (aviable now PICTURES Favorites Folder). The Current "Name" must be in the root from PictureFiles !	Oct 26 (6 days ago)	alwinker...@gmx.de
r87		add: SkinSettingsMenu a new option with shortcuts. (aviable now KIDS and RECORDINGS). The Current "Name" must be in the root from VideoFiles !	Oct 25 (6 days ago)	alwinker...@gmx.de
r86		changed: Covers, and PlaylistSlide now with Album, Artist, Title labels when Sliding (IdleTime 4 sec.)	Oct 25 (6 days ago)	alwinker...@gmx.de
r85		testing: to add multiimages from a Folder as Background - part_4	Oct 25 (6 days ago)	alwinker...@gmx.de
r84		adjustment: Font size in this Dialog Window (DialogSongInfo.xml)	Oct 24, 2008	alwinker...@gmx.de
r83		adjustment: Font size in this Dialog Window	Oct 24, 2008	alwinker...@gmx.de
r82		testing: to add multiimages from a Folder as Background - part_3	Oct 23, 2008	alwinker...@gmx.de
r81		testing: to add multiimages from a Folder as Background - part_2	Oct 23, 2008	alwinker...@gmx.de
r80		testing: to add multiimages from a Folder as Background - part_1	Oct 23, 2008	alwinker...@gmx.de
r79		add: speaker.png to the Visualization update: changelog.xml
r78		added: SkinSettings Function to disable/enable "Next Tracks" in the Visualization. changed: orange Text color to the MusicPlaylist Heading Label when Party Modus is enabled. added: Big Music-Progressbar at the Bottom Home Window.	Today (4 minutes ago)	alwinker...@gmx.de
r77		adjustment: DialogSelect Font Size and Window size. add: orange Text color to the Heading label -> Dialog Windows	Yesterday (25 hours ago)	alwinker...@gmx.de
r76		adjustment: ThumbsViews (Big and small) Font size	Yesterday (35 hours ago)	alwinker...@gmx.de
r75		fixed: Diffuse positions at the pictureSlide View. (focusedlayout and itemlayout)	Yesterday (35 hours ago)	alwinker...@gmx.de
r74		adjustment: Font size at the pictureSlide View.	Yesterday (36 hours ago)	alwinker...@gmx.de
r73		upgrade: Script lelaloader to v. 02	Oct 20 (46 hours ago)	alwinker...@gmx.de
r72		adjustment: add-Content Window - scrapper Cover added - part_2	Oct 20 (47 hours ago)	alwinker...@gmx.de
r71		adjustment: add-Content Window - bigger Fonts and Windows - part_1	Oct 20 (2 days ago)	alwinker...@gmx.de
r70		adjustment: MediaSource Window - bigger Fonts and Windows - part_1 - for the moment (finished)	Oct 19 (2 days ago)	alwinker...@gmx.de
r69		adjustment: FileBrowser Window - bigger Fonts and Windows - part_3 (finished)	Oct 19 (2 days ago)	alwinker...@gmx.de
r68		adjustment: FileBrowser Window - bigger Fonts and Windows - part_2	Oct 19 (2 days ago)	alwinker...@gmx.de
r67		adjustment: FileBrowser Window - bigger Fonts and Windows - part_1	Oct 19 (3 days ago)	alwinker...@gmx.de
r66		add: 2 Buttons to the playerControls (forward and rewind). add: Seek .png to the seekBar.	Oct 18 (3 days ago)	alwinker...@gmx.de
r65		adjustment: DialogOK more height. changed: Update Button in the Home Sub-Menu Accessories now other Link-Name.
r64		changed: default background image, resize image size. adjustment: Fontsize at SystemInformation window. animating: default Lelaloader thumbnail, HomeAccessories SubMenu.	Yesterday (21 hours ago)	alwinker...@gmx.de
r63		update: changelog	Oct 14 (2 days ago)	alwinker...@gmx.de
r62		delete: .psd Files	Oct 14 (3 days ago)	alwinker...@gmx.de
r61		testing: update script test test test	Oct 13 (3 days ago)	alwinker...@gmx.de
r60		add: Skin changelog.xml testing: update script test test	Oct 13 (3 days ago)	alwinker...@gmx.de
r59		add: simple Skin update function: finding @ Home->Accessories->Update .:LeLa:. skin. Its downloading the .Rar File to F:/LeLa/LeLa-0057/ (0057 its the rev_Number). Extracting is possible ! Please changed to the default Skin (PMIII) an copy the LeLa-0xxx Folder to the xbmc-Skin Folder. Another Big Thanks to "NESGES" !!! 	Oct 13 (3 days ago)	alwinker...@gmx.de
r58		changed: better blue color to the OSD Full screen Window. add: update script "lelaloader" - many THANKS !!! to "nesges" xbmc.de USER (in the extras Folder. update implantation coming soon). lelaloader Icon by me (djtoll). add: fanspeed Info label to the music Vis. 	Oct 13 (3 days ago)	alwinker...@gmx.de
r57		adjustment: many changed/adjustment with the labels in the vis. adjustment: simple zoom animation for this windows. it shows now bigger.
r56		add: ProgressBar to the BIG MediaOverlay (Music-playing).	Oct 11 (46 hours ago)	alwinker...@gmx.de
r55		changed: Font color	Oct 10 (3 days ago)	alwinker...@gmx.de
r54		adjustment: Font size in the SettingsCategory.xml	Oct 10 (3 days ago)	alwinker...@gmx.de
r53		changed: Skin-Credits Label/TEXT	Oct 09 (3 days ago)	alwinker...@gmx.de
r52		add: Lela Skin Icon to the Skin settings adjustment: Head Label in the Skin settings (FANART & VIEW TYPES) now colored (orange). The Button is now a label. Clearer Effect.	Oct 09 (3 days ago)	alwinker...@gmx.de
r51		adjustment: Font size to DialogProgress/SeekBar, Position changed PlayerControls between DialogSeekBar is Focus. And getting a new animation. PART 2	Oct 09 (4 days ago)	alwinker...@gmx.de
r50		adjustment: VolumeBar size and font size. adjustment: Home window "Big" music overlay Time duration font size and year label now canter at the cover bottom.	Oct 09 (4 days ago)	alwinker...@gmx.de
r49		adjustment: Font size to DialogProgress/SeekBar, Position changed PlayerControls between DialogSeekBar is Focus. And getting a new animation.	Oct 07 (5 days ago)	alwinker...@gmx.de
r48		add: SlideView to All Atributes @ the MusicFiles and MusicDB (part3)	Oct 07 (6 days ago)	alwinker...@gmx.de
r47		add: SlideView to All Atributes @ the MusicFiles and MusicDB (part2)	Oct 07 (6 days ago)	alwinker...@gmx.de
r46		add: SlideView to All Atributes @ the MusicFiles and MusicDB (part1)	Oct 07 (6 days ago)	alwinker...@gmx.de
r45		changed: Visualization - media info background image.	Oct 06, 2008	alwinker...@gmx.de
r44		changed: Visible Idle Time ListView-Icon/Thumbs @ Music Database (3 sec..) (Datenbank). and add a new dark diffuse Background. 	Oct 06, 2008	alwinker...@gmx.de
r43		changed: Visible Idle Time ListView-Icon/Thumbs @ MyVideos (3 sec..) (FILEMODUS). and add a new dark diffuse Background. 	Oct 06, 2008	alwinker...@gmx.de
r42		add: Funktion! Big Icons for The Default Home Buttons (with Idle Time 19 sec... and slide Animation)...PART-4 -> Disable/Enable in the Skin-SettingsMenu. Default is ENABLED	Oct 05, 2008	alwinker...@gmx.de
r41		add: Funktion! Big Icons for The Default Home Buttons (with Idle Time 19 sec... and slide Animation)...PART-3 -> Disable/Enable in the Skin-SettingsMenu.	Oct 05, 2008	alwinker...@gmx.de
r40		add: Big Icons for The Default Home Buttons (with Idle Time 19 sec... and slide Animation)...PART-2	Oct 05, 2008	alwinker...@gmx.de
r39		add: position Button @ Home-Submenus	Oct 05, 2008	alwinker...@gmx.de
r38		add: Big Icons for The Default Home Buttons (with Idle Time 9 sec)...PART-1	Oct 05, 2008	alwinker...@gmx.de
r37		add: a smily Icon over the DialogBusy Background (n the left).	Oct 05, 2008	alwinker...@gmx.de
r36		new: German Skin Language - importing from the English, not yet translate.	Oct 05, 2008	alwinker...@gmx.de
r35		adjustment: DialogBusy.xml, bigger Font and new Background. (Finished).	Oct 05, 2008	alwinker...@gmx.de

